Hello friends welcome back I am the name of the YouTube channel
so today I am going to tell you about
digital insurance
how you can claim its insurance
and what are its benefits and from where
you will get this app, you will get all this information in
this video so let's go to the
video and later
you will find its app on play store in which two of
its photos are given and kept, it will be original
so now I have opened the app, you have to
click on register here after clicking on register
you will see this type of screen
policy details will be there policy
start date will be there on the policy number you have to
note down the policy number in the policy paper you have to file the
start date of the policy from when it is starting you have to
file it there after that continue it
after continuing you have to enter the vehicle
registration number here
your RCB registration
card number you have to
enter it here after that continue
after continuing you have to enter the customer details here there is
accident
You have to enter the date of the accident that happened in the current situation, on
which date it happened, you have to
fill all this here below, you have to give the details of the service advisor, in the
service advisor details you have to
give the name of the service advisor who is working for
you on this service card, you have to
give your email ID and WhatsApp mobile number through
which the survey can contact you at night,
when the card number is entered, there is
a card number of it,
you have to see it there, you have to enter
the details of when the vehicle came to you, you have to
enter the P code, the
vehicle and the date from when and the estimated loss,
you have to enter it here,
after entering the estimated loss you have to continue,
after continuing you will
see the tax box here, from this you have to look at the vehicle,
after entering it here, it is
asking you to capture the photo of the front of the bike here, so
I will show you the method of capturing it
later in the video, so
after clicking on capture image, you have to
take a photo of the bike so that the bike is
completely captured, continue further in
this way  There are all the processes,
I am showing you this way.
After taking photos from all sides, you will have to
upload the photo of the vehicle here as well.
For that, you will have to go to capture image and turn on the
banana face as per your wish and
capture the photo of these as well.
You will have to upload the chassis of the bike here as well.
After doing all these processes, you will have to
upload the damage shown on the vehicle in the external damage here so that the company can
find out what all the damages have happened to your bike.
After uploading the photo of all the external damage, you will have to upload the photo of your bike here,
front side and back side.
After that, you have to file the details of your driving
license, that is, who was
driving the car during student time, here you have to upload the
front size and back
side of the license. You have to upload that of the license
here. If you have a police copy or if
you have a press request, then any
affair copy will also have to be uploaded here. It has been
generated now, so in this way you
saw how the digital